Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS 092
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XII: Library
  - Morris, Jan. Journeys. New York: Oxford University Press, 1984. (Box 24, Folder 482)
  - Mortuary Posts of the Giryama. New York: Friends of Bronx Community Art Gallery, April 28-May 20, 1978. (Box 24, Folder 483)
  - Motor Auto Repair Manual. Second Vintage Car Edition, 1953-61. New York: Motor, 1981. (Box 24, Folder 484)
  - Mrabet, Mohammed. Marriage with Papers. Trans. Paul Bowles. Bolinas, CA: Tombouctou Books, 1986. (Box 24, Folder 485)
  - Mueller, Cookie. Walking Through Clear Water in a Pool Painted Black. New York: Semiotext(e), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 486)
  - Muench, David, and Donald D. Pike. Anasazi: Ancient People of the Rock. Palo Alto, CA: America West Publishing Co., 1974. (Box 25, Folder 487)
  - Muktananda, Swami. Does Death Really Exist? South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1981. (Box 25, Folder 488)
  - ---. I Have Become Alive. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1985. (Box 25, Folder 489)
  - ---. Kundalini: The Secret of Life. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1979. (Box 25, Folder 490)
  - ---. Meditate. Albany: State University of New York Press, 1980. (Box 25, Folder 491)
  - Municipal Index and Atlas. New York: American City Magazine Corporation, 1940. (Box 25, Folder 492)
  - ---. New York: American City Magazine Corporation,1941. (Box 25, Folder 493)
  - The Nation. 13 Feb. 1989 (Box 25, Folder 494)
  - ---. 20 Mar. 1989 (Box 25, Folder 495)
  - The National Enquirer. 31 July 1990. (Box 25, Folder 496)
  - National Geographic [cover altered]. Vol. 154, No. 4 October 1978. (Box 25, Folder 497)
  - National and International Studio Programs 1983-1984: P. S. 1, The Clocktower. New York: Institute for Art and Urban Resources, 1984. (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - National Museum of Anthropology, Mexico. Mexico: GV Editores, 1986. (Box 25, Folder 500)
  - Neese, Robert. Prison Exposures. Philadelphia: Chilton Company Book Division, 1959. (Box 25, Folder 501)
  - Neo York: Report on a Phenomenon. Santa Barbara, CA: University Art Museum, 1984. (Box 25, Folder 502)
  - Neruda, Pablo. A New Decade Poems 1958-1967. Trans. Ben Belitt and Alastair Reid. New York: Grove, 1969. (Box 25, Folder 503)
  - ---. New Poems. Trans. and Ed. Ben Belitt. New York: Grove, 1972. [Pages 6 and 22 marked] (Box 25, Folder 504)
  - New Art Examiner. Nov. 1990 (Box 25, Folder 505)
  - New Narrative Painting: Selections from the Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York. Fort Lauderdale, FL: Museum of Art, 1984. (Box 25, Folder 506)
  - The New Press Catalogue. New York: W. W. Norton & Co., 1992. (Box 25, Folder 507)
  - Newsweek. 11 Mar 1985. (Box 25, Folder 508)
  - The New Wonder World Encyclopedia. Vol. 2. New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957. (Box 25, Folder 509)
  - ---. Vol. 3 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957. (Box 25, Folder 510)
  - ---. Vol. 4 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957. (Box 25, Folder 511)
  - ---. Vol. 6 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957. (Box 26, Folder 512)
  - ---. Vol. 10 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957. (Box 26, Folder 513)
  - New Year! New Talent! Celebrating Emerging Artists of the Eighties. (advertising supplement) (Box 26, Folder 514)
  - New York. November 5, 1984. (Box 26, Folder 515)
  - ---. June 22, 1987. (Box 26, Folder 516)
  - Nietzsche, Friedrich. Beyond Good and Evil. Trans. Walter Kaufmann. New York: Vintage Books/Random House, 1966. (Box 26, Folder 535)
  - Nilsson, Lennart. Close to Nature. New York: Pantheon, 1984. (Box 26, Folder 536)
  - O'Connor, Flannery. The Complete Stories. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1971. (Box 26, Folder 537)
  - O'Hara, Frank. Second Avenue. New York: Totem Press/Corinth Books, 1960. (Box 26, Folder 538)
  - October. No. 43 Winter 1987. (Box 26, Folder 540)
  - Oe, Kenzaburo. Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness. Trans. John Nathan. New York: Grove Press, 1977. (Box 26, Folder 541)
  - The Old Reliable Catalogue. Aug. 1990 (Box 26, Folder 542)
  - Organizaciechint. No. 229 Abril/Mayo/Junio. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 543)
  - Our Amazing World of Nature. Pleasantville, NY: Reader's Digest Association, 1969. [pages 25, 40, 46, 85, 131, 164-5, 199, 203, 207, 231, 265, 284-5, 302] (Box 26, Folder 544)
  - Outweek. No. 63 12 Sept. 1990 (Box 26, Folder 546)
  - Outwrite '91. [n. p. ] 1991. (Box 26, Folder 547)
  - Owen, Gale R. Rites and Religions of the Anglo-Saxons. New York?: Dorset Press, 1985. (Box 26, Folder 548)
  - Pacific Film Archive. Nov. /Dec. 1992 (Box 26, Folder 549)
  - Painting and Sculpture Today 1986. Indianapolis: Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1986. (Box 26, Folder 550)
  - Palmer, William M. Poisonous Snakes of North Carolina. Raleigh: State Museum of Natural History, 1974. (Box 26, Folder 551)
  - Panizza, Oskar. The Council of Love: A Celestial Tragedy in Five Acts. Trans. Oreste F. Pucciani. New York: Viking Press, 1973. (Box 26, Folder 552)
  - Paretsky, Sara. Killing Orders. New York: Ballantine, 1985. (Box 26, Folder 554)
  - Parkett. No. 21 1989 (Box 27, Folder 555)
  - ---. No. 27 1991 (Box 27, Folder 556)
  - ---. No. 31 1992 (Box 27, Folder 557)
  - Parkhurst, Violet. Painting Sunsets. Tustin, CA: Walter Foster, 1985. (two copies) (Box 27, Folder 558)
  - Pasolini, Pier Paolo. The Divine Mimesis. Trans. Thomas Erling Peterson. Berkeley: Double Dance Press, 1980. (Box 27, Folder 559)
  - ---. The Ragazzi. Trans. Emile Capouya. Manchester: Carcanet, 1986. (Box 27, Folder 560)
  - ---. Roman Nights. Trans. John Shepley. Marlboro, Vt: Marlboro Press, 1986. (Box 27, Folder 561)
  - ---. Roman Poems. Trans. Lawrence Ferlinghetti and Francesca Valente. San Francisco: City Lights, 1986. (Box 27, Folder 562)
  - ---. The Scent of India. Trans. David Price. London: Olive Press, 1984. (Box 27, Folder 563)
  - Patch, Edith M. and Harrison E. Howe. Science at Home. New York: MacMillan, 1937. (Box 27, Folder 564)
  - Pato Donald. 21 Apr. 1987 (Box 27, Folder 565)
  - Pauline's. New York: Pauline Bernatchez, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 566)
  - Pelton, Robert W. and Karen W. Carden. Snake Handlers. Nashville: Thomas Nelson Inc., 1974. (Box 27, Folder 567)
  - Perceptions: Black and White. Frances Wolfson Art Gallery. 1986 (Box 27, Folder 568)
  - Photography Annual. Photography Magazine. 1954 (Box 27, Folder 569)
  - Physique-Art. New York: Roto Color Corp., [n. d. ]., undated (Box 27, Folder 570)
  - Pickwell, Gayle. Weather. Los Angeles: The Junior Literary Guild, 1937. (Box 27, Folder 571)
  - Piero Manzoni. New York: Hirschl & Adler Modern, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 572)
  - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts. Fall 1983. (Box 27, Folder 574)
  - Platt, Rutherford et. al. Secrets of Life: A True-Life Adventure. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1957. (Box 27, Folder 575)
  - Playguy. Vol. 3, No. 12, undated (Box 27, Folder 576)
  - Polysexuality. Vol. IV. No. 1 Semiotext(e), 1981. (Box 27, Folder 577)
  - Pomerans, Arnold J., trans. A Small Yes and a Big No: The Autobiography of George Grosz. Feltham, UK: Hamlyn Publishing, 1982. (Box 27, Folder 578)
  - Pop, Iggy. I Need More. New York: Karz-Cohl Publishing, 1982. (Box 27, Folder 579)
  - Popol Vuh. Trans. Ralph Nelson. Boston: Houghton-Mifflin, 1975. (Box 27, Folder 580)
  - Portis, Charles. Norwood. New York: Vintage/Random House, 1985. (Box 28, Folder 581)
  - Powell, William F. How to Paint Clouds and Skyscapes. Tustin, CA: Foster Art Service, 1987. (Box 28, Folder 582)
  - ---. How to Paint Clouds and Skyscapes. Tustin, CA: Foster Art Service, 1989. (Box 28, Folder 583)
  - Pox. No. 61 [n. p. ], [n. d. ]., undated (Box 28, Folder 584)
  - Preston-Mafham, Rod and Ken. Spiders of the World. New York: Facts on File Publications, 1984. (Box 28, Folder 585)
  - Prignitz-Poda, Helga; ed. Frida Kahlo. Frankfurt: Neue Kritik, 1988. (Box 28, Folder 586)
  - Pringle, Laurence. Dinosaurs and Their World. San Diego: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1968. [Note page 35] (Box 28, Folder 587)
  - Purdy, James. Cabot Wright Begins. New York: Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1964. (Box 28, Folder 589)
  - PWA Coalition Newsline. Issue #57. Jul. /Aug. 1990 (Box 28, Folder 590)
  - ---. Issue #60. Nov. 1990 (Box 28, Folder 591)
  - QW. No. 44 6 Sept. 1992 (Box 28, Folder 592)
  - Rader, Dotson. I Ain't Marchin' Anymore. New York: Paperback Library, 1964. (Box 28, Folder 593)
  - Rand, Ayn. The Fountainhead. New York: Signet, 1971. (Box 28, Folder 594)
  - Rechy, John. City of Night. New York: Grove Press, 1963. (Box 28, Folder 596)
  - Redrum Magazine: The World of Archie. [n. d. ]; Redrum: The Time of the Assassins [n. d. ]; Redrum: The Charter Arms [n. d. ]., undated (Box 28, Folder 597)
  - Redtape. #4. Fall-Winter 1983-4., 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 598)
  - Rees, Paul K., Fred W. Sparks and Charles Sparks Rees. Algebra, Trigonometry and Analytic Geometry. New York: McGraw-Hill, 1967. (Box 28, Folder 599)
  - Re/Search: William S. Burroughs, Throbbing Gristle, Brion Gysin. San Francisco: Re/Search, 1982. (Box 28, Folder 600)
  - Resnick, Robert and David Halliday. Physics. New York: John Wiley, 1966. (Box 28, Folder 601)
  - Rey Rosa, Rodrigo. The Beggar's Knife. Trans. Paul Bowles. San Francisco: City Lights, 1985. [page 80 marked] (Box 28, Folder 602)
  - Richter, G. M. A. A Handbook of Greek Art. New York: Phaidon Publishers, 1960. (Box 29, Folder 603)
  - Rimbaud, Arthur. Illuminations and Other Prose Poems. Trans. Louise Varese. New York: New Directions/James Laughlin, 1957. (Box 29, Folder 604)
  - Ringgold, Gene and DeWitt Bodeen. The Films of Cecil B. DeMille. New York: The Citadel Press, 1969. (Box 29, Folder 605)
  - Ritter, Bruce. Sometimes God has a Kid's Face. New York: Covenant House, 1988. (Box 29, Folder 606)
  - Riverrun. s. l.: 1975. (Box 29, Folder 606A.)
  - Robert Frank. Boston: Little, Brown and Co., 1986. (Box 29, Folder 607)
  - Rodriguez, Arturo. Mitos en blanco y negro. Madrid: Coleccion arte original, 1979. (Box 29, Folder 608)
  - Rolling Stone. Issue 605. 30 May 1991., 1959 (Box 29, Folder 609)
  - The Rolling Stone Interviews. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1989. (Box 29, Folder 610)
  - Rose, Joel and Catherine Texier; Eds. Between C & D. New York: Penguin, 1988. (Box 29, Folder 611)
  - Rosenfeld, Charles, and Robert Cooke. Earthfire: The Eruption of Mount St. Helens. Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 1982. (Box 29, Folder 612)
  - Rosenthal, Mark. Anselm Kiefer. Chicago: Art Institute of Chicago, 1987. (Box 29, Folder 613)
  - Sackheim, Eric, ed. The Blues Line: A Collection of Blues Lyrics. New York: Grossman Publishers, 1969. (Box 29, Folder 614)
  - Sagan, Carl, and Ann Druyan. Comet. New York: Random House, 1985. (Box 29, Folder 615)
  - Saint, Assoto; ed. The Road Before Us. New York: Galiens Press, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 616)
  - Saint sstien dans l'histoire de l'art depuis le xv sie. Paris: Jacques Damase Editeur, 1979. (Box 29, Folder 617)
  - Samuels, Peggy and Harold. Contemporary Western Artists. New York: Bonanza Books, 1982. (Box 30, Folder 618)
  - San Francisco Review of Books. Vol. 16, No. 1 Summer 1991. (Box 30, Folder 619)
  - Scavullo, Francesco. Men. New York: Random House, 1977. (Box 30, Folder 620)
  - Schidor, Dieter, and Michael McLernon, eds. Rainer Werner Fassbinder: Querelle, the Film Book. Munchen: Schirmer/Mosel Verlag, 1982. (Box 30, Folder 621)
  - Scholder, Amy and Ira Silverberg; Eds. High Risk. New York: Penguin, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 622)
  - Schulz, Bruno. Sanatorium under the Sign of the Hourglass. Trans. Celina Wieniewska. New York: Penguin, 1979. (Box 30, Folder 623)
  - ---. The Street of Crocodiles. New York: Penguin, 1963. (Box 30, Folder 624)
  - Schwab, Gustav. Gods and Heroes: Myths and Epics of Ancient Greece. New York: Pantheon, 1974. (Box 30, Folder 625)
  - Schwartz, Eugene M. The Sound of One Mind Thinking. San Francisco: Strawberry Hill Press, 1981. (Box 30, Folder 626)
  - Science. 3 Feb. 1988 (Box 30, Folder 627)
  - Sculpture Show: Neue Skulpturen aus der East Village. Koln: Anna Friebe Galerie, 1984? (Box 30, Folder 628)
  - Segaller, Stephen and Merrill Berger. The Wisdom of the Dream: The World of C. G. Jung. Boston: Shambhala, 1989. (Box 30, Folder 629)
  - Seisser, Jean. Herve DiRosa. Paris?: Le Dernier Terrain Vague, 1983. (Box 30, Folder 630)
  - Serpent's Tail Catalogue. April-Dec. 1992 (Box 30, Folder 631)
  - 750 Warme Berliner. Berlin: Verlag rosa Berliner, 1987. (Box 30, Folder 632)
  - Seymour, Jacqueline. La Naturaleza: Los Hongos. Trans. Ramon Menal Armisen. Barcelona: Ediciones Castell, [n. d. ]., undated (Box 30, Folder 633)
  - ---. La Naturaleza: El Mundo Natural. Barcelona: Ediciones Castell, [n. d. ]., undated (Box 30, Folder 634)
  - Shepard, Sam. Motel Chronicles & Hawk Moon. London: Faber & Faber, 1985. (Box 30, Folder 635)
  - Sherman, Charles L. Nature's Wonders. Garden City, NY: Hanover House, 1956. (Box 30, Folder 636)
  - Shiny. No. 6 Spring/Summer 1991. (Box 30, Folder 637)
  - Shomer, Louis. Police Jiu-Jitsu. New York: Book-A-Mag Co., 1940. (Box 30, Folder 638)
  - Siddha Path. [n. p. ], [n. d. ]., undated (Box 31, Folder 639)
  - Sidenbladh, Erik. Les Bs de l'eau. Trans. Christian Bounay. Paris: Editions Robert Laffont, 1982. (Box 31, Folder 640)
  - Siegle, Robert. Suburban Ambush. Baltimore: Johns Hopkins Press, 1989. (Box 31, Folder 641)
  - Sigmar Polke. Koln: Josef-Haubrich-Kunsthalle, 1984. (Box 31, Folder 642)
  - Sloane, R. K. A Real Gein ~Zine. Albuquerque, NM: R. K. Sloane, 1985. / Smithsonian Scientific Series. Old and New Plant Lore. Vol. 11 U. S.: Smithsonian Institution Series Inc., 1931. (Box 31, Folder 644)
  - Smithsonian. Dec. 1975 [Note: AHobo article@] (Box 31, Folder 645)
  - The Snakes of New Jersey. Reprinted from New Jersey Outdoors. [n. p. ] [n. d. ]., undated (Box 31, Folder 646)
  - Social Studies: Truth, Justice and the Afro-American Way. Normal: University Galleries, 1989. (Box 31, Folder 647)
  - Space Images. New York: Lustrum Press, 1982. (Box 31, Folder 648)
  - Spiegelman, Art. Maus II. New York: Pantheon Books, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 649)
  - Spin. June 1991. (Box 31, Folder 650)
  - Splendeurs et Miss du Corps. Paris: Paris Audiovisuel, 1988. (Box 31, Folder 651)
  - Sproule, Anna. Wild Animals. London: Octopus Books Ltd., 1979. (Box 31, Folder 652)
  - Stanek, V. J. Introducing Monkeys. Trans. George Theiner. London: Spring Books, [n. d. ]. [source material], undated (Box 31, Folder 654)
  - ---. The Pictorial Encyclopedia of Insects. London: Paul Hamlyn, 1969. (Box 31, Folder 655)
  - Stephens, John L. Incidents of Travel in Yucatan. Vol. 1 &2. Mexico City: Panorama Editorial, 1988. (Box 31, Folder 659)
  - Stern [German-language magazine]. January 1984. (Box 31, Folder 660)
  - Stern, Jane. Trucker. New York: McGraw-HIll, 1975. (Box 31, Folder 661)
  - Stewart, James B. Den of Thieves. New York: Touchstone, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 662)
  - Stirling, Matthew W. Indians of the Americas. Washington, D. C.: The National Geographic Society, 1955. (Box 32, Folder 663)
  - Sturgis, J. E. Evangelistic Edition of Wonder Hymns of Faith. Cincinnati: The Standard Publishing Co., [n. d. ]., undated (Box 32, Folder 664)
  - Surgence. Paris: Aubin Imprimeur, 1991. (Box 32, Folder 665)
  - Sutton, Ann and Myron Sutton. Eastern Forests. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1987. (Box 32, Folder 666)
  - Swain, Ralph B. The Insect Guide. Garden City, NY: Doubleday, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 667)
  - Swami Dayananda and Janaki Vunderink; eds. Hatha Yoga. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1981. (Box 32, Folder 668)
  - Sweeney, James B. A Pictorial History of Sea Monsters. New York: Bonanza Books, 1972. (Box 32, Folder 669)
  - Szarkowski, John; Ed. From the Picture Press. New York: MOMA Press, 1973. (Box 32, Folder 670)
  - ---. Mirrors and Windows. New York: The Museum of Modern Art, 1978. (Box 32, Folder 671)
  - Takahashi, Mutsuo. Poems of a Penisist. Trans. Hiroaki Sato. Chicago: Chicago Review Press, 1975. (Box 32, Folder 672)
  - Tales from the Crypt. No. 2 Sept 1990. (Box 32, Folder 673)
  - Tanaka, Seiichi. The Avant-Gardes in New York. Japan: 1986. (Box 32, Folder 674)
  - Taxidermy for the Amateur. New York: G. Schoepfer, [n. d. ]., undated (Box 32, Folder 675)
  - Tedlock, Dennis, ed. Popol Vuh: The Mayan Book of the Dawn of Life. New York: Touchstone/Simon & Schuster, 1985. (Box 32, Folder 676)
  - Terra-Cotta Warriors and Horses at the Tomb of Qin Shi Huang. [n. p. ]: [n. d. ]., undated (Box 32, Folder 677)
  - Thinking of You. [n. p. ]: April House, 1976. (Box 32, Folder 678)
  - Third Text. Summer 1990. (Box 32, Folder 679)
  - 36 Works, 18 Artists, 6 Galleries, 1 Alma Mater. Bronxville, NY: Sarah Lawrence College Gallery, 1982. (Box 32, Folder 680)
  - Tillman, Lynne. Living With Contradictions. New York: Top Stories, 1982. (Box 32, Folder 681)
  - Tillman, Lynne. Madame Realism. New York: The Print Center, 1984. (Box 32, Folder 682)
  - Tillman, Lynne. Haunted Houses. New York: Poseidon Press, 1987. (Box 32, Folder 683)
  - Time. No. 29 21 Jul. 1986 (Box 32, Folder 684)
  - Time. No. 6 6 Aug. 1990 (Box 32, Folder 685)
  - Time. No. 7 19 Aug. 1991 (Box 32, Folder 686)
  - Tinbergen, Niko. Animal Behavior. Alexandria, VA: Time-Life Books, 1978. (Box 32, Folder 687)
  - Toboldt, William K. and Larry Johnson. Automotive Encyclopedia. South Holland: Goodheart-Willcox Co., 1983. (Box 33, Folder 688)
  - Tomkins, Calvin. The Bride and the Bachelors: Five Masters of the Avant-Garde. New York: Penguin, 1976. (Box 33, Folder 689)
  - Tom's Hard Choice. New York: Star Distributors, 1985. (Box 33, Folder 690)
  - Torso. Vol. 7, No. 12 June 1989. (Box 33, Folder 691)
  - ---. Vol. 8, No. 2 Sept. 1989;. (Box 33, Folder 692)
  - Townsend, Richard Fraser. State and Cosmos in the Art of Tenochtitlan. Washington, D. C: Trustees for Harvard University, 1979. (Box 33, Folder 693)
  - Trees and Flowers of the Hawaiian Islands. Honolulu: Honolulu Star Bulletin, 1944. (Box 33, Folder 694)
  - True, Webster Prentiss. The Smithsonian Institution. Vol. 1 Smithsonian Scientific Series, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 695)
  - Tunnicliffe, C. F. Wonders of Nature. New York: WM. H. Wise and Co., 1945. (Box 33, Folder 696)
  - Tupitsyn, Margarita. Margins of Soviet Art. Milan: Giancarlo Politi, 1989. (Box 33, Folder 697)
  - Turner, Kay and Pat Jasper. Day of the Dead--The Tex/Mex Tradition. [n. p.: The Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center, [n. d. ]., undated (Box 33, Folder 698)
  - Turner's England. London: British Museum Publications, 1980. (Box 33, Folder 699)
  - Uncut. Vol. 5, No. 3 Jan. 1991 (Box 33, Folder 700)
  - Undergear. Spring, 1989. (Box 33, Folder 701)
  - Valdez, Luis and Stan Steiner; eds. Aztlan. New York: Vintage, 1972. (Box 33, Folder 702)
  - Varney, Philip. Arizona's Best Ghost Towns. Flagstaff: Northland Press, 1980. (Box 33, Folder 703)
  - Vermeule, Cornelius C. Greek and Roman Sculpture in America. Malibu: The J. Paul Getty Museum, 1981. (Box 33, Folder 704)
  - Villase Victor. Rain of Gold. New York: Laurel, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 705)
  - Villegas, Daniel Cosio, et. al. A Compact History of Mexico. Trans. Marjorie Mattingly Urquidi. Mexico: El Colegio de Mexico, 1985. (Box 33, Folder 706)
  - Vintage. Fall 1990. Catalogue. (Box 34, Folder 707)
  - Virilio, Paul, and Sylvere Lotringer. Pure War. Trans. Mark Polizotti. New York: Semiotext(e), 1983. (Box 34, Folder 708)
  - Vogel, Amos. Film as a Subversive Art. New York: Random House, 1974. (Box 34, Folder 709)
  - Wagner, Frank. AIDS. Koln: NGBK, 1988. (Box 34, Folder 711)
  - Wagner, Richard. Das Rheingold. New York: Dover Publications, 1985. [source material, pages excised for piece] (Box 34, Folder 712)
  - Wall, Robert. Ocean Liners. Secaucus, N. J.: Chartwell Books Inc., 1977. [cover inscribed, see also pages 232-3] (Box 34, Folder 713)
  - Walther, Ingo F., Ed. Otto Dix. Koln: Benedikt Taschen, 1988. (Box 34, Folder 714)
  - Waters, Frank. Book of the Hopi. New York: Penguin Books, 1977. (Box 34, Folder 716)
  - Weber, Bruce. Stuart Davis' New York. West Palm Beach: Norton Gallery, 1986. (Box 34, Folder 717)
  - ---; curator. Arnold Newman in Florida. Boston: David R. Godine, 1988. (Box 34, Folder 718)
  - Weber, Bruce, and William H. Gerdts. In Nature's Ways: American Landscape Painting of the Late Nineteenth Century. West Palm Beach: Norton Gallery of Art, 1987[?]. (Box 34, Folder 719)
  - Weber, Theresa Lund. Pompei, Herculanum, et le Vesuve. Florence: Bonechi Edizioni, 1984. (Box 34, Folder 720)
  - Westwood, Jennifer; ed. The Atlas of Mysterious Places. New York: Weidenfeld &Nicolson,1987. (Box 34, Folder 722)
  - Wheat, G. Collins. The World of Ants. New York: Golden Press, 1959. (Box 34, Folder 723)
  - White, Curtis; ed. An Illuminated History of the Future. Boulder: Illinois State U, 1989. (Box 34, Folder 724)
  - White, Edmund and Adam Mars-Jones. The Darker Proof. New York: Plume, 1988. (Box 34, Folder 725)
  - White, John W. Argentina: The Life Story of a Nation. New York: The Viking Press, 1942. (Box 34, Folder 726)
  - Whitfield, Charles L. Healing the Child Within. Deerfield Beach: Health Commications, 1987. [inscribed] (Box 35, Folder 727)
  - Whynott, Douglas. Following the Bloom. Boston: Beacon Press, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 728)
  - The William S. Paley Collection. New York: The Museum of Modern Art, 1992. (Box 35, Folder 729)
  - Willock, Colin. La grande faille d'Afrique. Amsterdam: Time-Life, 1985. (Box 35, Folder 730)
  - Winkler, Arnim. Giotto. Trans. Anne Ross. New York: Crown, 1968. (Box 35, Folder 732)
  - Winterson, Jeanette. Sexing the Cherry. New York: Vintage International, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 733)
  - Wosien, Maria-Gabriele. Sacred Dance. London: Thames and Hudson, 1974. (Box 35, Folder 734)
  - Wojnarowicz, David. Sounds in the Distance. London: Aloes Books, 1982. (Box 35, Folder 734A.)
  - Wojnarowicz, David. Red M. New York: Red Herring Press, 1977. 2 copies. (Box 35, Folder 734B.)
  - Wojnarowicz, David. Close to the Knives. New York: Vintage, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 734c.)
  - Wright, Barton. Hopi Kachinas: The Complete Guide to Collecting Kachina Dolls. Flagstaff, AZ: Northland Press, 1977. (Box 35, Folder 735)
  - Wurman, Richard Saul. Cities: Comparisons of Form and Scale. Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 1974. (Box 35, Folder 736)
  - Yasuo Kuniyoshi: Artist as Photographer. New York: Morgan and Morgan, 1983. (Box 35, Folder 737)
  - Yearbook '53. School of Industrial Art. 1953 (Box 35, Folder 738)
  - Year of the Hopi. New York: Rizzoli, 1979. (Box 35, Folder 739)
  - Ylla. Animals in India. New York: Harper and Brothers Publishers, [n. d. ]., undated (Box 35, Folder 740)
  - Yogiraj Sri Swami Satchidananda. Integral Yoga Hatha. New York: Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1970. (Box 35, Folder 741)
  - Zim, Herbert S. Reptiles and Amphibians. New York: Golden Press, 1956. (Box 35, Folder 742)
  - Zone 1. Spring 1977; Zone 2. Summer/Fall 1977; Zone 5. Spring 1980., 1977, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 743)
- Series XIII: Objects and Artifacts
  Series XIII consists of objects and artifacts collected or created by David Wojnarowicz.
  Subseries A: General Objects and Artifacts. The objects in this series include religious objects, figurines, jewelry, toys, textiles, and artworks. While some of the objects are artworks made by Wojnarowicz, they also include artworks made by others, ritual objects, natural artifacts and commercial objects that he collected. Some of the objects figured as props in Wojnarowicz's photography and film works.